

#### Juan Insuasti

Bogotá, Colombia

(+57) 301 783 6169

juan.insuasti@gmail.com locke189.github.io

## **ABOUT ME**

Electronics Engineer with 4+ years of experience implementing IT solutions, development and deployment of enterprise applications. I am a self-taught, highly motivated person who is looking forward to facing new and demanding challenges in frontend development and UX design. Passionate about innovation through research and education.

## **SKILLS**

#### **LANGUAGES**

HTML5 CSS3 JS Python ABAP

## LIBRARIES / FRAMEWORKS

**BOOTSTRAP** SAPUI5

#### **TOOLS**

**GITHUB** 

# **JUAN INSUASTI** FRONTEND DEVELOPER

## **EXPERIENCE**

(2014 – present)

## **USER EXPERIENCE / SAP TECHNICAL CONSULTANT**

EY

Part of the SAP technical team in Colombia. Focused on user experience development, tools and methodologies to deliver new and innovative services to EY clients. Involved in SAP Projects as a SAP Frontend Developer and technical consultant.

(2012 - 2014)

## SAP TECHNICAL CONSULTANT

**IBM** 

Part of the Global Consulting Services SAP Team in Colombia. Design and implementation of the technical infrastructure for SAP systems, development of business applications and SAP backend administration.

## **EDUCATION / CERTIFICATIONS**

(2014)

## SAP CERTIFIED TECHNOLOGY ASSOCIATE

SAP

(1999 - 2001)

## **ELECTRONICS ENGINEER**

## PONTIFICIA UNIVERSIDAD JAVERIANA

## **PROJECTS**

Frontend Development

EY - Colombia - 2016

Consolidation EY's global and local support tools and resources to the Colombian employees.

SAPUI5 / Fullstack Developer

GoSCM - Mexico - 2016

SAPUI5 application to display Here Maps in SAP TM for freight orders.

SAPUI5/ Frontend Development

EY - Colombia - 2016

Medical History App using SAPUI5 for OpenSAP development challenge. (Top 220)